Week 4. Day 1. Our Little Green Friends. Appearance. Reduce. Photosynthesis. Carbon
dioxide. Oxygen. Absorb. Harmful. Chemical. Tropical. Adapt. Survive. Fern. Formaldehyde.
Option. Gerbera daisy. Money plant. Spider plant. Snake plant. Day 2. Bored but never boring.
Tomb. Mention. Document. Alongside. Variety. Path. Roll of dice. Tile. Monopoly. Property.
Trivial. Pursuit. Feature. Theme. Competition. Rent. Face-to-face. Day 3. Playing on the go.
Attached. Along with. Replace. Browser. App. Application. Various. Manage. Potential. Planet.
Disadvantage. Nightmare. Day 4. Plastic surgery. Common. Wealthy. Surprisingly. Surgeon. Horrific.
Injury. Confident. Untrained. Procedure. Result from. Implant. Commit suicide. Devastating.
End up. Day 5. The ancient art of the brush. Dynasty. Highly. Calligraphy. Bronze. Religious. Convey. Authority. Pine.
Smooth. Stroke. Order. Relive. Intimate. Day 6. Free running. Acrobatics. Prop. Interact with.
Obstacle. Parkour. Efficiency. Preservation. Ramp. Element. Scale. Flip. Athletic. Stunt. Dedicate. Solely.
Duck.